You're making things difficult for the Gu family
I'm not
Then what is it
I'm just removing myself from
the risks you created
Notify the bank to hold off on discussions
When is this notice going out
Right before I walked in
the lawyers already sent it to the bank
the regulators and both companies' emails
You already sent it
Yes
Risks will only escalate without an audit
Contact the project team immediately
Have the funds of Gu's affiliates
fully re-audited
Yes Mr Su
Uncle Su does this mean you don't trust the Gu family
There are ambiguous terms in the contract
A complete re-audit
is being responsible to both sides
I didn't come back to yield
I came to tell you
to stop making me take on
responsibilities that aren't mine
Don't get cocky Fu Chenzhou
You think he withdrew the guarantee for you
He did it for himself
That's enough for me
Yeah
Mr Gu the bank received the withdrawal notice
They require us to provide this afternoon
a financial statement of our affiliates
Several partners are also asking